languagenut.com 2018-02-09

# Privacy Policy - Languagenut America

**Privacy Policy**

**1\. INTRODUCTION**

We will treat all your Personal Information as confidential (although we reserve the right to disclose this information in the circumstances set out below). We will keep it on a secure server and we will fully comply with all applicable UK Data Protection and consumer legislation from time to time in place.

**2\. USING OUR SERVICES / PURCHASING PRODUCTS**

2.1. When you participate in our programmes or shop on this Website, we will ask you to input and we will collect Personal Information from you such as your name, e-mail address, school address, telephone number and a password. All such information must be correct when provided and we must be notified of any change following your first visit to this Website following such change.

2.2. We may also collect, and our third party providers of content may collect, information about where you are on the internet (eg the URL you came from, IP address, domain types like .co.uk and .com), your browser type, the country and telephone area code where your computer is located, the pages of our website that were viewed during your visit. We may collect this information even if you do not register with us.

2.3. You should be aware that this site is being monitored and may capture information about your visit that will help us improve the quality of our programmes and services.

2.4. We confirm that any Personal Information which you provide to us (or which is available on public registers) and any User Information from which we can identify you, is held in accordance with the registration we have with the Data Commissioner’s Office. We use your information only for the following purposes:

2.4.1. for statistical or survey purposes to improve this Website and its services to you;

2.4.2. for processing your continuing use of the Website;

2.4.3. for processing your purchase orders;

2.4.4. subject to your consent, to notify you of updates of new services and offers.

2.5. You agree that you do not object to us contacting you for any of the above purposes:

2.5.1. by telephone

2.5.2. by e-mail

2.5.3. in writing and you confirm that you do not and will not consider any of the above as being a breach of any of your rights under the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003.

**3\. YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

3.1. Your Personal Information may be disclosed to other businesses within the languagenut.com business and to reputable third parties involved in the delivery of our services to you. We require all such parties to treat your personal information as fully confidential and to fully comply with all applicable UK Data Protection and consumer legislation from time to time in place. We will not release your Personal Information to any company outside of the langaugenut.com business, save in respect of facilitating payment to languagenut.com for the services provided and products purchased from this Website.

3.2. Where you are making an online payment, we will direct you to a secure site provided by a registered reputable provider of payment services.

**4\. DISCLOSURE UNDER LAW OR REGULATION**

You should be aware that if we are requested by the police or any other regulatory or government authority investigating suspected illegal activities to provide your Personal Information and /or User Information, we are entitled do so.

**5\. COOKIES**

We use Cookies to keep track of your use of this Website and any shopping session to personalise your experience and so that you may obtain access to your training session or to retrieve your shopping basket at any time – if you do not accept Cookies you will be unable to use this Website.

Issue Date [05.05.17]
